tutcity.com 2016-04-11

# Privacy Policy :: TutCity.com

TutCity.com (hereafter referred to as TutCity) respect and is committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and used. We promise that we will take steps to use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy. 

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that TutCity does not own or control, or of persons that TutCity does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which TutCity's websites link. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

You can visit the TutCity without revealing any personal information. However, TutCity collects personal information when you register with TutCity. This is required if you wish to submit your tutorials, publish your work/tutorials, or use certain services. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the TutCity service, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

When you signup/register for a service, we will ask you for the these personal information: name and e-mail address. We may use your personal information to contact you for account purposes. When you submit feedback or questions via e-mail, or contact us for information about our Web site, we will request your name and e-mail address. We use this information solely to respond to your inquiries.

TutCity certifies that all personal information relating to its members and clients, including email addresses and personal information, will be kept confidential. We do not share, sell, rent or barter any identifiable personal information to any third party. 

From time to time, TutCity or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of TutCity's you have visited or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible.

Our advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) may also use cookies and/or web beacons to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers may use this information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site TutCity.com and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

By using the TutCity, you consent to the collection and use of information by TutCity as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

If you have questions or comments about TutCity's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
